

RAMI TALIH

Mobile phone

+971508754059 (UAE)

+9613743563 (Lebanon)

Address

Dubai, UAE

Email

rami.talih@gmail.com

Nationality Lebanese Date of birth January 9, 1989

ABOUT ME

With more than 7 years of Media Agency experience, working with a wide spectrum of clients from various industries, my career has led me to understand the inside out of the media industry in the region. I love to be challenged and have an ambition to succeed. I am seeking to work in the digital field, where I can grow and invest my acquired knowledge where professionalism, teamwork and commitment are rewarded assets.

WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2017 - Present

DELPHYS MIDDLE EAST

DUBAI, UAE

SENIOR DIGITAL MEDIA MANAGER

- Revived & Centralized Delphys/Drive Dentsu (Dubai, Jeddah & Riyadh) Digital Unit catering to all our clients across GCC market.
- Managing Toyota Motor Corporation (Toyota & Lexus) digital activities in the GCC.
- Worked on:
 - Media Strategy, Planning (Toyota, Frico, Sabic, ...)
 - Social media (starting from setting a strategy down to moderation and answering people)
 - Advertising (launching campaigns on Google, social media or regular platforms)
 - Leading the buying unit (Tactical deals & VR)
 - Training for individuals (clients and colleagues)

Feb 2014 – May 2017

MEDIA ZONE

JEDDAH, SAUDI ARABIA SENIOR DIGITAL PLANNER

Joined Media Zone as offline media planner before moving to the digital department. Throughout my career at Media Zone, I worked on a diversified portfolio of clients in terms of Strategy, Planning, Buying & Research across GCC market. That includes, TV, Radio, Print, OOH, Digital & Social Media.

June 2012 – January 2014

H&C LEO BURNETT

ACHRAFIEH, LEBANON

Junior accountant

Dec. 2011 – May 2012

GEAHCHAN & PARTNERS S.A.R.L.

HAZMIEH, LEBANON

External auditing, worked on VAT, E.O.S., Salary Taxes, and final audit report, etc.

EDUCATION

September 2018

CDMP (CERTIFIED DIGITAL MARKETING PROFESSIONAL)

Morgan Institute - Digital Marketing Institute

April 2017, March 2018

GOOGLE ADWORDS CERTIFIED

- Google Search
- Video certifications
- AdWords Fundamental
- June 2011

UNIVERSITY OF SAINT JOSEPH (BEIRUT, LEBANON)

Bachelor's in Business Administration

2008

COLLÈGE DE LA SAGESSE ACHRAFIEH (BEIRUT, LEBANON)

Lebanese Baccalaureate in Economic Science

LANGUAGES PROFICIENCY

- Arabic: native proficiency
- French: very good both spoken and written
- English: very good both spoken and written

APPLICATION SOFTWARE PROFICIENCY

- Skilled in all Microsoft Office applications
- Skilled in online tools like Google analytics, Sprout social, Social bakers, OOX, Effective measures,
 Narrative, Facebook Ads Manager, Twitter Ads manager, etc.
- Skilled in Ipsos Statex & X-Plan research software

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

USJ STUDENT COUNCIL

Student representative for the academic year 2009-2010 at the University of Saint Joseph.

LEBANESE RED CROSS

Emergency Medical Technician (EMT) at the Lebanese Red Cross since 2009. Team leader since 2012, mission leader since 2010. Also, got many responsibilities like ambulances and the depot of the station.

LEBANESE SCOUTS ASSOCIATION

Sixteen years of scouting experience from 1994 to 2010, where I evolved from a young cub to a unit leader. From leading a small group (Patrol Leader), I came on to lead a larger group of boy scouts whose ages vary between 11 and 17. I have received training as a patrol leader as well as a unit leader.

INTERNATIONAL BASKETBALL FEDERATION (FIBA)

Point-guard of the Chabibeh Country Lodge basketball youth team for two years (2006 to 2008).

EXTRA-CURRICULAR CERTIFICATES

April, 2011:

Rock climbing instructor, Ecole Francaise d'Escalade

July, 2009:

Dive Safety through Education, NAUI, World Wide

May, 2009:

Emergency Medic Certificate, Lebanese Red Cross

Sept, 2008:

Junior Life Saving, YMCA of Lebanon

June, 2006:

Professional Swimming Group, Honorary Certificate, Sporting Club.